http://www.dixiemed.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

Use code 25OFF500 for $25 off $500+ purchase     |     View all Promotions
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Effective Date: September 9, 2019
Introduction Cardio Partners is owned and operated by Sarnova. This cookie notice is specific to Cardio Partners. Cardio Partners (“we,” “us,” “our”) is committed to respecting the privacy of our users and to protecting the information you provide to us. This online privacy notice applies to information about you obtained through www.cardiopartners.com (the “Website”). This notice describes how we may collect, use, and disclose such information; the choices available to you regarding our use of your information; how we safeguard the information we collect; and how to contact us with any questions regarding our privacy practices. By accessing or otherwise using any of the Website, you agree to the collection, use, disclosure practices and other activities as described in this policy. If you are visiting the Website from the European Union or European Economic Area, you may review your rights and our privacy practices here. Information We CollectInformation You Provide to Cardio PartnersIn order to provide you with particular services, we may ask you to provide certain information to us. Personal information that you submit through our Website may include contact information, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, job title, and employer. We may also collect account and login information, such as your username, password, security questions, and basic details about your account. Some forms on the Website may require you to provide certain information in order to submit the form. You may elect to not provide this information but doing so may prevent you from using or accessing those features. In order to access some of our services or purchase our products, you may also be required to provide us with payment information, including credit card number, billing address, shipping address, and other information necessary to complete a purchase. Cardio Partners takes great care to protect this information and does not store payment card information after it has been processed for order fulfillment purposes. We collect the aforementioned personal information from you so that we can serve you better, and so that we can provide you with customized services. For example, we may ask you to provide certain personal information when you wish to purchase a product, when you request a repair service, or when you subscribe to one of our newsletters. Should you choose to enroll in our voluntary rewards program, we will use your basic contact information to track your purchases and accumulate points to your account. We also use the information you provide us to initiate returns, issue product safety notices, and communicate with you. You may also provide us with information when you send us messages or inquiries, or when you apply for a job with us. Please note that any personal information provided to Cardio Partners in a message format (e.g. through a “Contact Us” form) will be used only for the purpose of responding to your message. Information Automatically CollectedCardio Partners may also automatically collect certain information about you when you access or use the Website (“Usage Information”). Usage Information may include your device identifier, IP address, browser type, location (country only), operating system, and other information regarding your use of the Website. We may obtain this Usage Information through the following means:
Log information. Log information is data about your use of the Website, such as IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, operating system, date/time stamps, and related data. Log information may be stored in log files.
Information collected by cookies and other tracking technologies. Cookies, web beacons or “tracking pixels,” embedded scripts, location-identifying technologies (country only), device recognition solutions, and other tracking technologies (“Tracking Technologies”) may be used to collect information about your interactions with the Website. Brief descriptions of these Tracking Technologies are provided below.
CookiesCookies are small text files that may be stored on your computer, smart phone, or tablet when you access the Website. This information can be read by the Website when you return to them. Cardio Partners uses cookies to speed up your future visits by storing preferences and login information you provide, and to support a better experience through tailored content. In addition, cookies provide statistical and other information to Cardio Partners about how the Website is used in order for Cardio Partners to monitor access and use of the sites, assess the effectiveness of particular content, and suggest areas for improvement. While these cookies alone do not allow us to personally identify visitors to the Website, information collected by cookies may be used to streamline communications with our clients and customers by facilitating targeted content, such as suggested products, consistent with users’ presumed preferences and this privacy notice. Cookies may remain on your hard drive for an extended period of time. The Website may associate some or all of these cookies with your device(s). If you use your browser’s method of blocking or removing cookies, some but not all types of cookies may be deleted and/or blocked and as a result, some features of the Website may not be available. For more information about cookies, visit: http://www.aboutcookies.org/. Click here to review our Cookie Policy. Web Beacons (“Tracking Pixels”)Web beacons are small graphic images, also known as “internet tags” or “clear gifs,” embedded in web pages. Web beacons may be used, without limitation, to count the number of visitors to the Website, to monitor how users navigate the Website, and to count content views. Embedded ScriptsAn embedded script is programming code designed to collect information about your interactions with the Website. It is temporarily downloaded onto your computer from our web server, or from a third party with which we work, and is active only while you are connected to the Website. It is deleted or deactivated once you are no longer connected. Device Recognition TechnologiesTechnologies, including application of statistical probability to data sets, as well as linking a common unique identifier to different device use (e.g., Facebook ID), which attempt to recognize or make assumptions about users and devices (e.g., that a user of multiple devices is the same user or household). Location-Identifying TechnologiesGPS (global positioning systems) software, geo-filtering and other location-aware technologies locate (sometimes precisely) you for purposes such as verifying your location and delivering or restricting content based on your location. Our content may be personalized based on various information we may have about you to try to provide you with more location-relevant content. Some information regarding your use of the Website and certain third-party services may be collected by Tracking Technologies across time and across our different services. Cardio Partners and third parties may use this information to assist you with account log-ins, to track and accumulate your loyalty points, and to offer you products we think may interest you. Apart from collecting Usage Information, we do not automatically collect information from users who are visiting public areas of the Website and who do not affirmatively provide us with more information. This Usage Information is used exclusively for internal purposes, such as analysis of clickstream data and website optimization. Information Obtained from Third Parties In limited circumstances, we may obtain information about you from service providers, business partners, or other third parties. For example, we may obtain job applicant data from LinkedIn, Glassdoor, and other career platforms where we have posted listings. How We Share Your InformationThird Party ProvidersCardio Partners may share information about you (including, without limitation, personal information we collect) for any purposes not inconsistent with this privacy policy or our statements at the point of collection, and not prohibited by applicable law. In general, we use your information to provide you access to the Website and its services, to optimize and improve the Website, to tailor features to your preferences, to communicate with you, and to offer you information, opportunities, promotions, and increased functionality. In order to do these things, we may disclose your personal information to third parties that we use to provide some of the services on or through the Website. For example, we may use third parties to help us analyze site visitor and associated Usage Information, to facilitate customer service, to conduct promotional email campaigns, conduct customer surveys for internal use, and to help us optimize the Website. We may also share payment card and other necessary information with an outside payment processor. Service providers are not permitted to use personal information received from us, except as necessary to provide the relevant services to Cardio Partners. We do not share personal information with third parties to use for their own purposes (e.g. marketing). Other Necessary CircumstancesWe may also disclose your personal information if we believe, in our sole discretion, that such disclosure is necessary and/or appropriate in the following circumstances:
To comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or court orders served on us;
To respond to requests from government agencies, including law enforcement authorities;
In connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is or may be illegal, or which may expose us, our service or content providers, or you to possible legal liability;
If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements, applicable terms, or policies; or
To protect the rights, property, life, health, security, or safety of Cardio Partners, the Website, users of the Website, or any third party.
In the event we sell or transfer a portion of our business assets (e.g. in the course of a merger, reorganization, liquidation, or any other business transaction, including negotiations of such transactions), we reserve the right to disclose any information we obtain through the Website. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and are permitted by and subject to this privacy policy.
Links to Third-Party SitesCardio Partners’ Website may contain links to other websites, including those of third-party organizations which are separate from Cardio Partners. Cardio Partners is not responsible for the content, privacy practices, or data collection practices of those sites. We encourage you to read the applicable terms and privacy policies before using those linked sites.
API Services
Cardio Partners' Website utilizes YouTube API Services to place YouTube videos on product and information pages. You can view YouTube's Terms of Service here, and review Google's Privacy policy here.
Social FeaturesCertain features of the Website permit you to initiate interactions between the Website and third-party services, such as social networks (“Social Features”). Social Features include features that allow you to click to and access our Facebook page, and from there, to “like” or “share” our content located on the Facebook platform. We may also have features that otherwise connect the Website to a third-party service (e.g., to push or pull information to or from the Website). If you use Social Features, and potentially other third-party services, information you post or otherwise provide access to may be publicly displayed by the third-party service you use. Both Cardio Partners and the third party may have access to certain information about you and your use of the Website and the third-party service.
Please note that Cardio Partners does not control who will have access to the information that you choose to make available to others on our third-party pages and cannot ensure that parties who have access to such information will respect your privacy or keep it secure. We are not responsible for the protection, accuracy, use or misuse of any information that you disclose to or receive from third parties through our third-party pages.
Advertising and AnalyticsWe may serve advertisements on the Website and/or on third-party services, which may be targeted based upon cookie data or other information we have obtained about you through means described herein.
We may use Google Analytics, Informz web tracking, HotJar, or similar tools to help us analyze and assess user interaction with the Website. These analytics services may use cookies and other Tracking Technologies to gather information about you and other users. Information collected or generated by these services (e.g., your IP address and other Usage Information) may be transmitted to and stored by these service providers, who may in turn use this information for purposes such as evaluating your use of the Website, compiling statistical reports on the Website’s activity, and providing other services relating to Website activity and other Internet usage.
Your ChoicesEmail Communications
Should you choose not to receive promotional emails from Cardio Partners or any of its affiliate entities listed above, you may opt out of receiving additional promotional email communications from us by following the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our emails. You may also contact us directly at privacy@cardiopartners.com. Please note that even if you opt out of receiving promotional communications from us, we may continue to send you non-promotional emails, such as those related to your orders or product inquiries.
Tracking Technologies
Regular cookies may generally be disabled or removed using tools available as part of most commercial browsers, and in some instances may be blocked in the future by configuring certain browser settings. Browsers offer different functionalities and options, so these may need to be set separately. Tools from commercial browsers may also not be effective with regard to Flash cookies (also known as locally shared objects), HTML5 cookies, or other Tracking Technologies. For information on disabling Flash cookies, please visit here. Please be aware that if you disable or remove these technologies, some aspects of the Website’s functionality may be limited. Your browser settings may also allow you to transmit a “Do Not Track” signal when you visit various websites. Like many websites, this Website is not configured to respond to “Do Not Track” signals received from browsers. To learn more about “Do Not Track” signals, please click here.
Analytics and Interest-Based AdvertisingYou may exercise certain choices regarding the use of Google Analytics cookies by visiting this page, or downloading the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.
SecurityCardio Partners takes reasonable measures to protect your information from loss, theft, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Our secure server uses advanced encryption and firewall technology to keep your personal information private. Our secure server layer (SSL) software completely encrypts the information you input so that it cannot be read as it travels to our ordering system. We have extremely strong security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information while it is in our control. However, Cardio Partners cannot guarantee “perfect security” and cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or others through the Website. Such information is transmitted at your own risk.
Children’s Privacy Rights The Website is not intended for, nor targeted to, children under 13. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect information from children under 13. If we learn that we have received information directly from a child who is under the age of 13, we will delete the information in accordance with applicable law.
California Privacy RightsWe do not share personal information as defined by California Civil Code Section 1798.83 (“Shine The Light Law”) with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.
International UsersIf you are visiting the Website from outside the United States, please be aware that Cardio Partners is based in the U.S. and the information we collect will be transferred to, processed, and stored on our servers in the United States. The data protection laws and regulations applicable to your personal data transferred to the United States may be different from the laws in your country of residence.
AmendmentsCardio Partners reserves the right to change this privacy notice at any time. The revised notice will be effective at the time of posting to the Website.
Questions and Concerns
If you have questions regarding this policy, or if you believe that Cardio Partners has handled your personal information in a manner that does not comply with this policy, please notify us by email at privacy@cardiopartners.com or by mail at:
Cardio Partners1001 Flagpole Ct.Brentwood, TN 37027
Get The Latest News
Stay up to date with the latest articles and news from the AED Blog.
Submit
Quick Links
Click on any icon to learn more.
AEDS
CPR Certification
Service
LifeShield Login
